Characters, actions, places, occupations, and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
I just lost a Sports Day match.
You don’t have to comfort me.
Free hugs.
You're the best in my eyes, P’Niran.
Did you lose a Sports Day match today?
What did Coach Ong call to tell you this time?
What are you looking at?
Haven’t you ever seen a 12th-grader cry?
I’m sorry.
I let you cry for so long.
I want to be by your side at a time like this.
Today, I’m going to be that planet
that helps absorb your tears.
Let this planet be flooded.
We’ll float together.
You have stars in your room.
My dad made them for me when I was a kid.
That’s great.
Your dad is so sweet.
I have some more stars like that.
If you like them,
you can put them up in your room too.
Do you have a headache?
Why would I?
I just cried. I’m not sick.
Most people get headaches when they cry.
Cheewa, are you really single?
I’m single. Why do you ask?
Well…
You seem to take good care of people.
Have you been like this
since you were a kid?
Well, my parents take care of me like this.
Are you saying you’re my parents?
No.
I’m just saying my parents
take care of me like this
because they love me
and want the best for me.
When I love someone and want the best
for them, I want to take care of them too.
Hey, Cheewa.
Yes?
Can I sleep here tonight?
I don’t want to go home and see my dad yet.
Of course.
You can stay for as long as you like.
As long as I like?
You can stay for eternity.
♪ I can feel it too ♪
♪ There’s someone to see me through ♪
♪ I have nothing to fear ♪
♪ Because I hold you dear ♪
♪ I always feel safe here ♪
I want to take a shower.
Can I borrow your clothes?
Sure.
Give me a second.
Wait, do you mind if I sleep in your bed?
Make yourself at home.
Do you know them?
Are they a boyband?
Yeah, I think so.
I love them so much.
I’ve seen them. They’re handsome.
Who’s the most handsome?
Hey!
You and I need to talk.
Following Mr. Oy from the Boxing Club
being bullied by an unseen entity,
information was circulated
throughout the school
that it was the doing of
the science building’s ghost.
Initially, Mr. Oy has accused Mr. Niran
from the Judo Club of being behind it,
forcing us from the Astronomy Club,
known as the Universe Court,
to step in and urgently find a solution
to this situation.
You call this urgent?
They nearly beat each other to death.
Is he obsessed with Judge Bao
or something?
No idea.
Since neither side has any evidence
to prove their case,
we have to hold a hearing today.
What the hell is wrong with you now, Oy?
I want to end this already.
At first, it just annoyed me,
but now it’s affecting my life.
I get bullied every day.
You have to prove it.
And get the science building kids
to help.
So my friend is being accused of
being the culprit?
Do you have evidence that my friend did it?
I don’t.
You don’t have any evidence,
but you won’t stop accusing him?
If it’s not your friend, who could it be?
There’s no one else.
You say that a lot.
It’s ridiculous, you know?
Even a kindergarten kid
is more reasonable than you.
Yeah.
Even though I’m stupid,
I can still think better than you.
And my friend is stupid.
Excuse me?
Hey!
You saw me come alone,
so you're ganging up on me, assholes?
Exactly.
If you came with more people,
how could I fight you?
Stop arguing already.
It’s such a waste of time.
P’Niran, you really didn’t do it, did you?
You’re sure?
Of course.
Can you swear to it?
Are you really a science kid?
Why are you making me swear?
Come on.
Just swear.
Swear before the universe.
It’s greater than anything else.
Nonsense.
My friend isn’t going to do anything that silly.
Yeah.
If I did it,
I hope I fail my exams, have to repeat
a year, can’t go to university,
and get stuck here for another year.
Sadhu!
Great. You can be stuck with Cheewa
for another year.
Have you ever told the teachers about this?
Your mom is a teacher.
Have you tried telling her?
My mom won’t believe me.
I’m not good enough in her eyes.
I’m a piece of shit.
That’s true.
I guess I’ll have to get beaten to death
before she believes me
Please don’t talk like that.
Let’s just talk about catching the culprit.
Fine. I’m just complaining.
Why are you taking it so seriously?
How about this?
Since Oy couldn’t find any evidence
to accuse me,
I’ll find evidence myself
to prove that I’m not the bad guy.
That’s it.
How will you proceed?
I’ll track down the real culprit, of course.
But what if the real culprit is a ghost?
We have to look for a ghost?
Hem.
Listen to me.
Don’t be delusional.
Ugh. Ghostbusters.
I can’t with my friends.
I have a plan.
P’Niran.
Hmm?
Are you sure you’re okay?
About what?
About what P’Oy said in the club room.
Oh, I’m fine.
I get him.
Just his words can't make me
think anything bad.
Are you worried about me?
Yes.
Why are you worried about me?
If I don’t worry about you,
who am I supposed to worry about?
I like you.
Stop it.
Go home.
Are you coming?
It’s about to rain.
I have an umbrella.
No need for an umbrella. Run!
Come on!
Oh, Glasses.
Did your mom already give you
her wedding invite?
Um…
Dress nicely. Find something nice
to wear to her wedding.
I’m not going.
How could you not go?
She’s your mom.
I don’t want to go.
Come on.
Don’t act like a child.
You’re a grown-up.
Your mom is getting married.
Go congratulate her.
At least go out of courtesy.
If you’re happy for her, you go.
I’m not happy.
I’m not going.
Damn it.
Why does this have to happen to me?
You can’t sleep?
Yeah, I’m a little frustrated.
Is something wrong?
(You can tell me.)
I don’t know how to explain.
Can you just stay still
and let me hear your voice?
(Is that any good?)
(I’ve been practicing this song.)
Huh?
What did you ask again?
P’Niran,
I asked if you liked it.
Um…
I do.
Yeah.
So do I.
(P’Niran.)
Yes?
I meant what I said the other night.
What a great service.
Do I have to pay for staying over?
Feel free to pay with your heart.
Cheewa,
are you this straightforward
about everything?
Don’t you get shy at all?
I am.
Do I make you uncomfortable?
No.
I actually respect you for it.
You’re not afraid to speak your mind.
I’ve never seen you beat around the bush.
Did you know?
The average human lifespan is 78.1 years.
If you keep beating around the bush,
it’s like you lose
20% of your life.
Oh…
20%?
So there’s 60-something years left?
62.5 years.
Okay. I give up.
Nong Cheewa is always right.
Next time,
you can be straightforward with P’Niran.
P’Niran gets it now.
I can be straightforward
about everything, right?
Yes.
I like you, P’Niran.
I really do.
Cheewa,
do you know what I asked my mom
the day she was about to leave me?
I asked how much I had to love her
for her to stay with me.
How much I had to love her
for her not to leave me.
I’d love her that much.
But in the end, she’s still gone.
Even though I love her that much,
she still left me.
Do you understand me, Cheewa?
Everyone I love
might all be gone.
Please understand me, Cheewa.
I might need some time,
but I’m really trying
to work through a lot of things.
Take as much time as you need, P’Niran.
But that whole time,
(I’ll be right here for you.)
Please let me go with you.
I’m worried about you.
If something happens, I can protect you.
The Universe Court
has come to the conclusion
that Mr. Niran from the Judo Club can prove
his innocence by finding the real culprit.
Hmm?
The accused has to
prove his own innocence?
What kind of court is that?
What do you say, P’Niran?
Boxing Club.
I think the one who bullied him
is someone close to him.
You guys have to help me.
You’re way off.
It’s my club. Who would dare bully me?
Thara,
go pretend to work out in their area
and keep an eye out for me.
Thipok,
go join the Boxing Club.
Will that be convincing?
What if they catch on
that I have an ulterior motive?
What if I get beaten up by their coach?
You won’t.
This is our special coach.
Coach Henry.
Yeah.
Hello.
My name is Henry.
What about you?
What are you going to do?
Me?
I’m going to observe from the outside.
Too many people in there
will make things messy and blow our plan.
Yeah. Easy for you to say.
We’re the ones who have to
play these random roles.
I think that’ll be a waste of time.
Let’s go with another plan.
But I think there’s a reason
the culprit is someone from your circle.
Like P’Niran said.
Because Oy is…
What?
Cover your ears for a second.
Cover your ears.
Yeah.
Oy talks so much shit
and has a shitty personality.
He’s so unlikeable.
And he still has the nerve to insist
that no one would dare
make an enemy of him.
So it has to be someone close to him.
Who the hell could stay close to him?
Just being around him is freaking annoying.
Damn.
Not to mention how he looks.
Are you done?
Yeah.
I’m done.
I’ll stay with you, P’Niran.
You don’t have to.
You can stand by with your friends.
Once I catch the culprit,
Jomyut can interrogate them.
Please let me go with you.
I’m worried about you.
If something happens, I can protect you.
Who’s protecting who?
Henry!
Let’s go push up!
Do you think they’ll pull it off?
Of course, they will.
Come on.
Did you make them do this on purpose?
No.
Let’s focus on catching the culprit.
Yeah.
He’s so weird.
Yeah, Oy is being crazy again.
All he does is pick on Niran.
It’s freaking hilarious.
Yeah, and he thinks Niran did it.
I’m losing it.
But does he not suspect you at all?
Not at all.
He’s freaking stupid.
Wanna go to the bathroom?
Yeah.
Come on!
Are they gone?
Not yet.
Can I get up now?
I don’t think they are.
Really?
Are they gone?
I think we should keep hiding like this.
It’s safer.
I don’t think so.
Let’s go.
I’m so damn hungry.
What are you guys eating?
No idea.
You pick.
I’ve picked enough.
Crispy pork basil.
No, noodles.
Again?
Noodles? Please.
You two eat that shit all the time.
Again?
You two pay.
Oh, look what I’m wearing.
You want me to pay?
I don’t have any money.
It’s Naw.
Come on.
I don’t have anything to do with this.
Hey!
Let go!
What the hell are you guys doing?
Shut up!
Please.
Turn on the lights
and stop shining that on my face already.
My eyes sting.
No!
Just confess.
You’ll get a lighter sentence.
Confess?
About what?
You guys haven’t told me anything.
Are you idiots?
About me.
Oh.
Hey, Oy.
Why are you with them?
Is there something you want to tell me?
Tell you what?
Let’s go back to our club.
Most of the time,
Oy gets bullied
when he passes the science building.
So we have to lure them
to the science building.
Your job
is to pretend you don’t know you got caught
and drag them over here.
What the hell are you talking about?
You do know
that P’Oy has been bullied this whole time
and he blames P’Niran for it.
Today,
we heard you talk to your friends
from your club.
About what?
If you’ve got something to say,
just f*cking tell me.
If you really have nothing to do with this,
I’ll beat the shit out of them.
Excuse me?
So much for helping you.
Well, Oy likes to put people down in the club.
You have to own up to it, man.
You really do that.
You’ve gotten on everyone’s nerves
in the club.
I’m going to catch them red-handed.
Just tell us what to do.
Here’s the plan.
Oy, you’ll be the bait.
And you, Naw.
Go back to your gang
and tell them to bully Oy again.
As for you guys,
record some evidence,
in case we need to send it to the teachers.
Leave the rest to me.
What about us?
For you two,
if they run,
split up and spread out.
Stop all of them.
Everyone involved in this.
Mission accepted.
We won’t let you all down.
You think you can pin this on me,
you science building ghosts?
You’re going to die in this building
all over again.
No!
I’m afraid of ghosts.
Your hair smells nice too.
And how could you smell someone’s hair
without asking?
Next time, I’ll ask first.
Oh.
You cheeky kid.
So you guys are the ones
pretending to be the science building ghosts.
This time, I’ll leave him alone.
I’ll join you guys.
You sure?
We can do it ourselves like usual.
But I think that sounds fun.
Yeah.
This time, we can invite everyone.
Anyone who hates that jerk.
That’ll be too many people.
The whole freaking club.
Let’s go. What are we waiting for?
How do we use this freaking camera?
I don’t know.
Why didn’t you ask Newton
when you took it?
Shit, I forgot to ask him.
Are you okay, P’Niran?
It’s really dusty in here.
Not to mention the smell of old books.
I’m fine. No worries.
Why?
Do you want me to smell your shirt
like when we were at the Boxing Club?
Do you want to?
Oh.
You cheeky kid.
My shirt smells nice.
I know it does.
I was smelling it for a while.
So you really do like this smell.
What?
Your hair smells nice too.
I was wondering what was tickling my head.
Turns out it was your nose.
Yes.
I was smelling it for a while.
Hey, don’t get smart with me.
And how could you smell someone’s hair
without asking?
I’m sorry.
Next time, I’ll ask first.
What do you mean, next time?
You two must’ve forgotten
that I’m sitting here too.
When are Naw and the others coming?
I want to get out of here.
Are you hot?
I’m sick of your love, Cheewa.
Mm.
He’s smiling at me, Hem.
Go ahead and smell each other’s hair.
Are you sure Oy is in there alone?
Yeah. He’s alone.
Let’s f*cking get him.
Let’s go.
Go!
Shit, they’re here.
Hold on.
We don’t want them to see us.
Whoa!
Shit, it’s vinegar?
Ouch!
Damn it!
F*ck!
Hey!
Shit, open it!
There’s way more of you than me.
What’s there to be afraid of?
What are you afraid of?
Fight me one-on-one!
Damn it!
So you guys are the ones
pretending to be the science building ghosts.
Shit, it’s Niran.
Where do you think you’re going?
Let’s go down the other side.
Why the hell are you guys blocking us?
Move, you four-eyes.
Damn it.
Did those assholes run away?
Follow them.
Don’t let them get away.
But I need to get away from you right now.
What the hell is that smell?
Go take a shower.
Shit.
Hey! Why are you standing there smiling?
Just go!
You all have tainted
the science building’s reputation.
You deserve to be punished.
They’re over here, P’Niran!
Why the hell did you tell him?
Catch them!
Close the door.
There are so many of them.
F*cking annoying.
I’m so damn exhausted.
It’s really you guys, huh?
What the f*ck are you rambling about?
Naw, go get the others.
We’re going to f*ck them all up.
Am I your friend?
Someone who puts others beneath them
isn’t someone we call a friend, Oy.
You’re so mean you don’t even realize it.
You f*cking piece of shit!
Can’t you handle the fact
that nobody wants you?
Nobody sees you as a friend.
Are you done rambling?
Let me punch you already.
You’ve been pinning the blame on me
this whole time, asshole.
P’Niran, don’t.
I’ll deal with him for you.
Asshole, aren’t you taking it too far?
Hey!
What are you guys doing?
You don’t go to your judo practice,
but you have time to fight with other people.
Aren’t you going to be good again?
Hello.
Oh—
Where’s P’Niran?
I’m afraid I can’t let him get away with it.
Niran has been sent to the principal’s office
several times for the same reason.
I’ll have to punish him
according to the school’s policy.
I understand.
I’d like to apologize to the school again.
HUMAN RESOURCES DIVISION
Hello.
Let’s go home.
Let me go get my bag first.
Um…
P’Niran!
Go back to class, Cheewa.
It’s not P’Niran’s fault.
The whole thing happened because—
It’s okay.
Teacher Suchart told me everything.
Go back to class, Cheewa.
I got this.
You don’t go to your judo practice,
but you have time to fight with other people.
Aren’t you embarrassed?
Huh?
Aren’t you going to be good again?
No, I’m not.
What are you even saying?
Huh?
Judo is your dream.
Whose dream?
It’s all your idea, Dad.
What’s wrong with you, Niran?
Look how far your friends have gotten.
You’re not going anywhere at this rate.
Do you know that?
Can’t you see that?
Have you ever once asked me
what I wanted?
All you do is say
I’m not good enough, I don’t try.
Why?
If one day I fail,
you’ll leave me like Mom did, right?
Right?
- Hello.
- Oh—
Where’s P’Niran?
He got out of the car
and stormed off somewhere.
Thank you.
Wait.
P’Niran!
♪ Whenever you need me ♪
♪ Just know I’m keeping you in my sight ♪
♪ No matter how dark it might be ♪
♪ Just look up at the sky ♪
♪ I asked every star ♪
♪ To care for you where you are ♪
P’Niran has worked everything out, Nong Cheewa.
Then we can go celebrate now, right?
Hey.
What are you spacing out about?
I’m quitting judo.
Even if there are more things you feel like you’re not good at, that’s okay.
I’ll cheer you on for eternity.
P’Niran, did you know—
P’Niran knows.
He knows you’re worried about him.
P’Niran is so lucky to have you, Cheewa.
Are we boyfriends yet?